Tell me how you think I'm wrong When I say I feel so lost
Tell me why you think you're love Do you erase all that it cost
Tell me why you look at me Like I'm just a piece of dust
Tell me how you think you know When I give away my trust
Gonna die one day
Oh darling, one toke over the life
You're gonna die one day. Sorry. I didn't mean to die on your screen. You'll help my ratings good. I'm sorry. I'm died
I did I didn't
But you're a witty would she like be bed ridden after she was that you should just be laying in bed
Do you just bring it? You should be dead right? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, I'm gonna have
I said bed ridden bed ridden bed ridden. What do you mean?
Like she's not gonna be able to get out of bed. She's gonna be so fat that she can't even get off my face when she's sitting on it
She's been I'm gonna die one day, you know
It's gonna be a thing. It's gonna be like she's just like oh god. Let me get off of you. I'm suffocating you
But you know I die under her ass
Well does anybody in chat guys you relate to this anybody have
Oh, god. Bro, like, you want to understand this, but it made me so happy. It's just so, like, so good. My, uh, my buddy, he, I guess my buddy, the silver owner, where I'm hanging out, like, it's different. It's a very, I'm on days he was different.
RPServer, I guess and so you don't kill everybody and
Yeah, hit me up. I
Like to do this like money outfit. You have to find clothes and like cut them up and
And then there's like a torch that I want to get, you know
Yeah, I got to get like gasoline to put on it to like increases durability, you know, they're half way that it
Like if you just made it with a stick and a rag
It'll do like I have to have to their real durability, but anyway, so yeah
He hit me up, bro. He put me in this like little spot that spawns all my shit and just
I don't have to do that anymore
So beautiful. I love it. It was such a relief. It was such a good thing
Mm-mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm
Where's everybody? Well, my notifications probably aren't going out right now because I got poor bombs or not poor bomb it and we're bombed and then
Alex came on and started saying you me looks like a transgender
And then she said she was gonna unalive him a few times and then somebody in the chat sort of threatening that they were gonna like report
That she threatened to murk him or whatever. And so I deleted that stream. I had to lead all the stream today. Oh
Yeah, I don't know where everyone is
Hold on. I mean, I don't know if this one's appropriate to play, but I'll try one more.
They put, they've actually put urgent protecting our community and why I left that. Okay, let's try these two.
They can't really go back and forth while I do that. How are you guys doing?
Yeah, so I mean I have to bet Alex. I mean it's like it's unfortunate
But it's like well first of all he was saying easy. He was saying you were
He was saying easy was porn bombing me. He was sure but I was like no it was Tony's voice
I know Tony's voice. He's he's like no easy porn bombs me and just like no reason then he said burdo is
raging demon and
Then and I said I thought it was so dumb. I was like, okay. Well, whatever. I don't care
He's like, well, you know, it's a gold mine if you like find that figure out who's who I'm like
No, it's not as dumb and then he started attacking you me
And for no reason decided no words. Oh, she's a trans la la la and uh, oh
Yeah, that's why it's okay. I'll sleep. It's on place. I'm gonna pull my dick out
Yeah, can you intervene? Keep an eye on him. It's a chat. Talk to the chat. You know what I'm gonna do
I'm gonna pull my dick out better or not. How fast can you?
Like delete the clip or whatever win while you're wanting to save the video
Just don't even talk about that. Can you delete none of your business?
Okay, I can't I can't I can't leave this guy first like
There's one more
Who the fuck do you think you are you're trying to like talk to me like what I
Can't be with a skinny bitch. I'm
Fill with a fucking bottle like growing up. I don't give a fuck about
Size zero I
Enjoy fat bitches
I didn't say I didn't say you I just said it was I thought the story was shot
Like you put it a very very very like you think that I can't get with fucking like I never said any
I consider good-looking bitches. It's like shut the fuck up. You're a nobody like
You can look at me. You can see I look way better than any of you motherfuckers
Well, I don't think it's not here. It's not shit compared to me
Just because I like a fucking
Hey, what I could take your bitch like any fucking bitch that any of these losers that have I've taken I
Don't walk them
I love that bitches. It's not so hard to understand. You're so fucking stupid. You can't understand that a
God likes
fat bitch
Fucking retard lady. You're a weirdo. Yeah, pedophile
Insane
Yeah, the cocaine he's chill a little bit, huh? Well
You know
It's like I just had enough of like, you know, look if this thing now it's like
I'm really it's like this. I don't know how like the show got about like people insulting each other like that
Which are the worst things I mean that person, right? I
Know it's like that, but it's not it though. There's seriously this is there's a mental disorder
I'll read it to you. It works where you think like everybody is somebody else and it's like really sad actually
Think everyone's like
It goes like this it's called
It's called
Hold on. No, it's the same. It's alert. Okay. It says neurological conditions called Frigoli delusion
So here are the Pregoli delusion guys. Oh shit. I'll fix it. I'm sorry
The Pregoli delusion. Okay. This is I've actually our family knows somebody that Pregoli
Oh
the hell
Pregoli delusion I
Don't know why it's doing that
Sorry, so I'm looking for goalie delusion, but I just have to um
Hold on easy easy. I'm gonna do something. Hold on
But can you like got my back? Hold on
If you ever see like that kind of comment
Just get my back. Okay, you know what to do. You know what to do. Okay
Yeah, so I got it hold on
I mean, I'll take care if you know what I'm talking about, you know, you know, you know, okay, hold on
Can you take care of that for me?
Okay
Is this live? Yes, it's live. Okay
Thank you
Yeah, you know, yeah, you know what to do. So anyway, for goalie delusion, I'm going to read about it because this is like, this is what Alex has, like he has this mental thing, it's called not saying anything wrong, maybe fun of any with mental disorder, but it's like, I want you to know, because when you hear him talking and going on and on about this, it says for goalie delusion, a rare neuro psychiatric disorder is a delusional belief that a familiar person is disguised as multiple people.
People with Frugoli delusion may misidentify several people as the same person in different disguises, often believing the person is intentionally following them.
The delusion can cause significant distress and impaired daily functioning. It's often accompanied by paranoia and anxiety and can lead to assaultive behavior toward others, right? Okay.
So this is like, is this, can it be any more spot on?
The Fragoli delusion or Fragoli syndrome is a rare disorder in which a person holds a delusional belief
that different people are in fact a single person who changes appearance or is in a disguise.
The syndrome may be related to a brain lesion.
and is often of a paranoid nature,
with a delusional person believing themselves persecuted
by the person they believe is in disguise.
A person with Frigoli delusion
may also inaccurately recall places, objects, and events.
This disorder can be explained by associative nodes.
The associative nodes serve as the biological link
of information about the other people
with a particular familiar face to the patient.
This means that any face that is similar
to a recognizable face to the patient,
the patient will recall that face
than they know. The Frigoli delusion is classified both as a monothematic delusion since it
only encompasses one delusional topic and as a delusional misidentification syndrome,
a class of delusional belief that identifying misidentifying people, places, or objects.
Like the Capgras delusion, psychiatrists believe it is related to a breakdown in the
normal facial perception.
So it says signs and symptoms, delusions, visual memory deficit, deficit and self-monitoring,
deficit and self-awareness, hallucinations, deficit and executive functions, deficit and
cognitive ability, history of seizure activity and epipyloctenogenic activity. Okay, something
has to do with dopamine sometimes, dopamine and a traumatic brain injury. There's other reasons
treatment you need like antipsychotic drugs basically it was named after the
Italian actor the opoldo for goalie who's renowned for his ability to make
quick change the appearance during a stage I now okay there's there's one side
of that that is the delusion there's another side of it that sometimes it
does happen right depends it can happen
with, you know, people like, you know, playing different parts, I mean, I think that'd be very, very, very rare, like, you know, that it's like, you know, someone, people are coming into the skies is trying to fuck with somebody.
I mean, maybe, I mean, maybe it's more common to like on the online world too, you know, because it's like, you know, you can disguise your voice.
We know there's people with voice changers. I know there's people in the community that are different people, but I don't think they're so obvious about it.
They'd be just similar to other people in a certain way, right?
And I'm not trying to call Alex like anything like it's not anything but I say Alex it is like
It's you're sounding insane. Like, you know, oh flirty diamond is burdo now burdo is
Raging demon. Okay, and like burdo you have to like know burdo someone and it's like burdo is like, you know
Basically a drag queen and like, you know, I don't even know what state but obviously raging demon is like a British
Or muslim British muslim and stuff
Easy's not looking down on you. Easy's just it's not looking down on you. What are you saying KZ?
And what KZ still and KZ was making this comment like and somebody still is like
Mool and Emma's but also um, what is like the thing about KZ is like? Oh, I was saying oh pores like what it what?
It's poor people you call poor people pores and like why would you bring it up in that context? I just don't know still
They're her poor people refer to as poor
Like pores like pores are like on your face, right?
So I'm not sure
Okay, keep an eye easy keep your keep your eye out. Hey Velo though
You don't know Emma you hate
What I hate poor not wait. Oh my god. Okay, so now now know it now it comes out now
It comes out now the truth feelings come out KZ
Don't know Emma and you're the one. What do I what do I pours?
So that's the original thing where it's like I was like, why are you saying that like I you have a
It's Casey, I mean people always reveal themselves, right homie
You got a new bond cool
By Casey
I mean, it's like, that's why it's like, it's like,
he just wanted to come back in.
Do you see how the attitude he got just then?
Okay, I was like, well, what did you actually mean by that?
When you actually, you confront somebody on there,
on their words, because he came back on my,
on my post and was like, oh, I meant this, I meant this.
And I was like, okay.
Well, yeah, you won't get in contact with them
I mean you can you can kind of go to our discord and she'll see your messages
And maybe we'll she'll reply to your messages, but you're not gonna like talk to her any extensive thing unless you
They see charges like $10 to talk to her cash up. Oh
My god
The end of the world. I'm actually thinking of like Kate
I'm just like ending my discord and then like starting this thing called communities and it's like I think I need to like limit access to me because
Some people take advantage of it, you know actually not they're not too bad, but
I think it's better to be have a have a look I do think it's better to have a laxus or people will
Hi Veldoh, so you got a new bond cool
Yeah, I mean, it's like I would have more people guys, but it's like when you start like the third live within 24 hours or something or
For 34th or something and this is my fourth or third or fourth
You know, they um, they don't put out the notifications because it would be like too many notifications for the same person
I guess within 24 hour period and so that's why there's fewer people in the chat right now
It is cool. It's like chill. Hi summer. How are you? I got your link for you
oh shit it's 5 a.m. yeah well it's only 3 a.m. here so it'd be almost 6 a.m. over
there right I know but look what I have it having my second affogato coffee here
Okay, well, thank you bellow though. Nice to meet you
Yeah, so I had to end already because I got and we're bombed by Tony and then he tried to come on again as
Alex and but then I had the real Alex up that it was just just as bad as might have oops might as both than Tony
Because he starts harassing you me. Hey, so sorry summer hold on
What up
I don't know, mate. Things went really slow. I'm sorry, Summer.
Hi.
Oh, fuck it.
Hello, hello.
I just woke up.
Hi, how are you?
Good! I just woke up. I passed out apparently last night.
I don't know what I was listening to, but I fell asleep.
Well, I yesterday I slept like I took so many naps yesterday
I think I must have taken like five or six naps and every time I would sleep just for about an hour or time and I'd have really
Crazy dreams and stuff like that and like kind of like the dreams would continue like, you know
On each nap they would kind of continue on in a chronological thing. It's pretty cool
but uh, yeah, and so and then I had these two big uh, big copies for dinner basically and
So I'm awake, but yeah, I had to delete my earlier streams because I got n-word bombed again
Who would they claiming to be?
No, you've been labelled right?
I've been a few times. I went live a couple times earlier and then but I had to delete the leap them all
I was one for like two hours and on it on for another hour and then Alex like you know, you me
I Alex actually made you me so mad. She was like, I'm going to unalive you a few times and then somebody was like threatening
You know, oh, she's threatened. She's making a threat and stuff. So
I deleted it, but yeah, it's like I can't I don't know and then Alex was like saying bizarre things like he was like
oh, you know raging demon is burdo and
You know, he's all this got all this figured out and like I was trying to like he just
You know, he once he saw it rage
He thought flirty diamond was burdo at one point and then he thought flirty diamond was actually this other guy
Glow
But waste so much time on it. I don't yeah
Troll he's not here to help you
Okay, I've been friends with Alex longer than you have ever probably would be
Um, me and Alex have already got a couple years and already thought about and everybody used to be like summer
Why the fuck do you still deal with him? And I have
Everybody counts out
Uh-huh you lost sound
My tablet's going super slow right now. I do apologize
Me
I must switch thoughts.
I don't know what happened. I
Jumped down to switch phones
Okay. Yeah, I don't know
Alex's a throw. I've known Alex you met Alex through me. I've known Alex for a very long time
And Alex was not gonna change, you know, that's why I stopped having him on my panels and stuff as much as I care about him
As much as I like them. I just can't anymore. You know what I mean? Yeah, yeah
You know, he hasn't been around in a couple weeks and well clearly ain't shit change. So
I just can't
Well, yeah, he's pretty much taking me to the breaking point too, or it's like, you know, and it's like I'm so forgiving
It's like it's like I even was like I think I had sick back on tonight
I think for like like two minutes and it's like, you know, he just can't
He's he's gonna be him too. You know, it's like you can't change people. They're not gonna be nice
They're not gonna behave themselves. They're always gonna like say something stupid like when you give them another chance. It's like
And I keep doing I keep hoping like
Well, sometimes they do seem to improve a little bit or like they'll you know, they'll be nice one day or something like that
We'll just throw it throw off your whole like balance and stuff like that and then
You know, I'm like even I'm like, I just want people to be nice
Basically, I don't know. That's like or be kind at least, you know, it's like, you know, just like be cordial be I
Don't know it's like some people you don't have to tell and then there's people that you can never tell you
You know, they'll never get it and it's like but I want to thank you for always being
kind cordial, you know, at least even if you've been mad at me, like it was like, you know, tough love kind of thing where it was like, you know
Yeah, I mean, I've always anything I've ever got, you know, whatever we've got into a little bit
It's because I care about you and I just see you doing the same stupid shit
It's like the meaning of insanity. I don't know what you think you're different than me or anybody else that's came across
Alex or any of these other people, but they're gonna be who they are
and you, you know, I get people talk about me, I get people call me a trafficker, I get people,
I mean, say anything and everything about me, you know what I mean? And I've just gotten finally
after a nervous breakdown online, after all kinds of other bullshit, I finally have been like, you
know what, I don't give a fuck, you better just say what you want of me. What you can't do is
You know I mean and they're gonna drive you crazy because they know
Emotional people like us impasse like us people or vampire energies, you know like they're just gonna suck all the energy about you
You know I felt that today like when I was like
I just was like all down to like, you know stream it and I was like, you know excited into the stream and then like
Like certain comments like just like all of a sudden I just felt all drained
And I just had to go back to sleep because I was like it just like took everything out of me like it's like it's just like
It's like you can feel it like it's like a real energy thing. It's like
And some since I think sometimes I sit back and watch you and I get it to an extent because I've done it as well
But I think you're trying to control something you created something one way now granted you could change things, right?
But I think that you're trying to control things that just be as beyond your control on the internet especially
Right, and I think I think that you because of that because it's become beyond your control
I think you're allowing it to eat you up
You know what I mean?
Well, it does.
It's got to.
It's not personal.
It's not personal anymore.
Yeah, it's not.
But if it was just about me, like, you know, my personality defects or my personal foibles
or whatever, it'd be one thing.
But it's like really slandering, like the business.
And then it's like, are people that making fun or like harping on like, oh, you're using
too much AI or, you know, it's like, you know, we don't like this.
Yeah, but Nike, okay.
Yeah, again, you're putting too much energy in the wrong shit
Like you're concentrating on what people are saying about your AI or this or that or this at the end of the fucking day
Those people are gonna come regardless. You know why they're gonna come because they know they can fuck with your head
And as long as you allow them to have that power, they're gonna continue to do it
Yeah, it's just an interesting community because it's like, you know, there's people like us that are like, you know
We get like the you know, we can we know how to troll too and it's like, you know, so it's like not like
You know, it is it's like a fix. I don't know it affects me in a different way
It's just like because it's like it's just sick is a constant like wearing down and it's like I kind of felt like I was like
I like a lot different than any other creator in this community, sweetie
You're just not you know, we do we all deal with the same things
And if you remember correctly in the very beginning when you kept screaming
I want a Howard Stern show and we kept saying psyche. Come on, dude like
And you were like, nope, this is what the fuck I'm going to do.
And this is it.
And so you did it.
And now it's not, but it's not even that.
It's like, it's like Jerry Springer.
It's not Howard Stern.
Howard Stern is like, you know, I had like, it is Howard Stern.
Well, with some of it, but it's like, it wasn't like, you know, but I say, I still,
and I say, I was still would like, you know, I.
kind of a Howard certain type of show, but I'm talking about having interesting
guests that are kind of like, you know, a lot of, like some of them are kind of
wacky or like, you know, have, you don't head first into the Abbey to community.
Where did you think that was going to happen at?
Because that's where I, that's where I, that's where I started at.
Cause of Benny, you know, I was like, Benny's was IP two.
And then that's why I met him.
And then he was the first person to help him with my show.
And then I got into like, you know, Joker and the Joker's on IP two.
And then, and I'll beat it and then I found.
Eat it through there and stuff. Yeah, your community what you build out of
is from that
You made that choice but it's also some like you know sometimes have long those choices sometimes have long
long consequences
Well, it's kind of like where I was born in a way on YouTube, right?
And it's like so it's like, you know
You're kind of a product of your environment in a certain way and it's like and then you go look kind of up to people like
You know kind of like a child looks up to their parents like oh, they're doing something
I want to be like them someday that kind of thing
And, you know, I was, I thought I watched Benny and I was like, you know, he was like,
here he is like 20 and he was like getting, you know, like a lot of people in his chat and
this like, you know, people interested in him and like, and he was basically just like sitting
there watching TV and hardly talking at all. Sometimes he talks more than other times,
but it's like, and I was like, I can like be interesting and like, you know, talk to people
and like, you know, and, you know, I've kind of like, well,
Think I've done pretty well
Looking at two people right and this is what I tell people all the time first of all
I'll be honest with you. I would never accept anybody sitting there saying like
Well, you know, I've looked up to so many people and this is what I want
Okay, but you should know better than anybody the things that happen behind the scenes
Just because you see somebody in the way they things the things are on YouTube or a celebrity or a radio show or any of this shit
None of it is what to what it seems to be on surface anybody that's ever built anything regardless of how you built it
That's I mean it is what it is
I just think that you personally are putting too much into and and I'm a supporter regardless
And I'm gonna be here regardless because I love you did that
But I think you're allowing your emotions these people to take your emotions and just run all over the place with it
And what's crazy is and I ain't gonna say no names
But it's just it's I give you advice like this and even when I've gotten it gotten in your ass
It's been so you could avoid shit like this, but you didn't see that
Remember like I'm still quite new, like new to it.
And so I came in a little bit and I, you know, no, no, no, no,
you're not new to this.
You're not new to this community.
You're not new to any of this, actually.
This is exactly what you wanted.
Like you, you got what, but I, but I, but I am, I am new to
stream, I wasn't new to streaming.
Yes.
And it was like, you know, the show is still like the show I want.
I mean, it's like, you know, still like, and I can do anything I want with
the show and I'm doing, I'm doing stuff on the show.
what I get disappointed in is like, you know, because it wasn't just like, you know, Joe Schmo
or anything making fun of me for the AI songs, it was Bita, you know, it's like, you know,
It's a part of an internet dude. Who gives a shit you
That's that's my because that's my friend. That was both what I thought was my friend and then second
But at the same time you also know how all your friends are just like me, you know, I'm gonna be spunky or
Spicy I'm gonna come up here. I'm probably gonna talk my shit
I'm gonna whatever you're asking people to be things that to treat you differently
My friend my friends not to like
Like I mean, but psyche come on dude come on like what?
Like what like really like it's like to laugh at me like
Okay, you want me to be all the way rule with you and all the way honest with you here lately
It's like we can't even have good fun panels
You know just like even paid shots to come through I try to come through all kinds of people try to come through
None of us matter and we haven't mattered for a long time. You've kicked me off the panel
You've kicked me off the panel you pay just fucking like
No, hold on. Let me finish. Let me finish because of people like Alex
You took stock at the people like alex and booted us the fuck off you allowed him to sit here and go
Ham on people that truly had your back and then you expect people's not gonna clap back
Come on, dude
You made your bed you're sleeping in it now
And I don't mean that I don't mean that in no foul way, but I'm just being honest like dude
We beg you
And this is what you want. Yeah, you
Wanted the SIGs and the and the you know all these other fucking crazy-ass people and we beg you we beg you
We got into it with some of these people to protect you
Yeah
You told us we wouldn't wait. This is your show. You're gonna do it. Yes, you did
You've kicked all of us off the channel before you've allowed Alex to sit here and go insane on us and not just Alex other people as well
And you you're you're in your fee fees because beta gets in her feelings and says, you know
Talks shit about you. Well, how you think she felt when she felt like you didn't have her back when you she was on your own panel
I felt that way. Hey, I'm sure it's felt that way. I'm sure all the people that really truly some it's like you concentrate on these
Idiots more than you concentrate on the people that have your back
All we have somebody has to do is come up here and flash a couple dollars to you
And you go let them do whatever fuck they want and you don't care about your friends getting hurt
But now, that you're sitting by yourself, you give a shit.
Well, that's the consequence of your actions, sweetie, and I'm not trying to be a bitch, I'm just being honest.
Easy, easy, easy, easy, let, easy, let Christine handle it.
Okay, I'll read that one.
Christine barely comes around, all of us.
Because we don't feel like having people like Alex, or even when Ghost is in his bullshit.
All he has to do is throw you some money, and we can treat him like half the fuck we want it.
No, I mean, it's not really not true. It is though. It's very
Christine am I lying I
Know anybody that has his fucking back. Am I lying? I'm not
Chris you know, yeah, I mean you're not lying, but you have a different perception of things and we're allowed to have a
I have a perspective of be coming on my friend's panel and him giving fuck more about money
Then he gives a fuck about what's got what's being said. That's not that's not true
That's not true, and it's like and the thing is summer. It's like you're I consider you like strong women that can
You know and it's like from the beginning like I would try to like okay, but you're a strong person too
And everybody has their week moments when we're sitting here
You told me you told me you brought the panel
We begged you to kick Alex off
You had them up here all night
Well tonight, yeah, I had to shut down the show, but that was because of you me, but it was an reaction to him
But yeah, that's my point
Everything's a reaction to him. You see like the people that there's someone backstage right now
Like like yeah, it's just like I know who it is
It's it's just a Tony back over and over again now now saying I'm promising someone your free reading and like you know
Blah blah blah. Hey Christine. Yeah, it's me. Hey, um, that's not Tony
I believe it's Alex in your view. It might be Tony with him
Just an FYI, a lot of what some are saying is truth.
You can get up
I'm not saying I'm saying yeah, maybe okay, but what I was trying to explain is that okay?
So I had piranha on and stuff like that and piranha and beta and when they were on the channel like I would like say
You know instantly if somebody called them a bit a bitch or something like that or a guy would instantly like step in and like you know
Tell the perfect, but you know or stuck and they're like
No, they're like, don't get involved.
They're like, we can handle ourselves.
Like they honestly did.
And from then on, I was like, okay.
I was like, if I white knight or whatever about it,
it's like, and then that looks like
they can't defend themselves.
And so I just had this thing is like,
I like when you guys get like feisty or whatever,
or like, you know, get back at or like troll back at them.
I think that's entertaining.
I didn't know that some people would go so far
and so personal with some of the things they said.
And it's sometimes it's just shocking for me.
And I don't know if also there's a relationship
where you guys have said stuff like that to each other
and stuff like that, like with like, you know,
Arthur and her and stuff like that.
I thought Arthur and her were friends
and then all of a sudden like the Bita and Arthur, right?
And then all of a sudden-
Yeah, but you know something Arthur
from the very beginning has not liked me
and I never have done anything to that man
and how he puts me down.
When Arthur's around, I normally stay away
or I purposely go up.
But just to irritate him, I don't say anything to him.
I don't only do anything to him.
That's pretty much it.
And as for Alex, same thing.
I won't go.
If I see Alex in a channel, I will not go in any way, shape,
or form.
He is evil.
I don't know if his brain, I don't know what's going on and I don't care because his evilness
He has teamed up with evilness that has been affecting me
Like and but and this is also the same thing and I mean is currently like
This is what psyche wanted though, so I can't even bitch what did I want I thought what I was not what I
Didn't I didn't understand what I
Yeah
But it's not even like a list anymore
Don't gas like me because one minute you don't understand and the next minute
this is the community you were birthed in. So you need to make your mind up which one it is.
Okay, well, you know, I P2 with anything and I can keep up with the conversation.
Here's, here's what I knew as I P2. I know, I know Benny, I knew Trident, a new saint. And,
and so, and it's like what they get a little bit drunk, they get a little bit wild, they go on an
RV. That's all. And then I knew like a Lisa was on it, but I didn't know. So I didn't know the whole
story. Yes. And it's like, and then I just, all I see is like, yeah, it's a website that in this,
Like I said, I
Did I not try to tell you to Christine not try to tell you I mean shit me and DJ don't even get along
But I'm pretty sure she even said something to you
Well, you know lecture is like, you know really
No, she doesn't like talk to me like you know like that like I don't know she she
She's this she's been very supportive of me and like very I don't know
I think she gets me on another level, but um, but I understand like it looks bad like you know, because I was like
You know, I seem like I'm like, you know
I don't even know why we have these conversations with you. I really don't I really feel like it's just a waste of space
Okay, well, I'm sorry like I was just explaining. I love you to death. I really do it
I'm a support you regardless at no regardless, but I mean
Maybe DJ will give you some advice.
And I support. I just don't support our chat.
She gets me in a different way where it's like, you know, it's like when I was being attacked for a lot of different things, like when I was being attacked for the Tracy thing and everything.
And it's like, and she, and it's like when...
No, but you were being held accountable for some of the actions that you caused.
That she came through a coddle to that's what you're saying. Oh my bad. I'm sorry
You can't have accountability from your friends because what you did to Tracy was bogus
No, I didn't do anything to Tracy. All I did was to Tracy was refund her money
I refunded her what I mean, I don't understand what the issue was I refunded her and so that was it
I mean, it's like that was the whole thing is like refund Tracy. That wasn't that the whole issue
I was like I'm going to as soon as I can't and then I
I know and it kept Alex off, but that was my mistake.
But Alex, as always, Alex Bucking ruins everything.
Well, you know it's like he won't anymore like because it's like I had enough when now that he's like you know
When he called you me like a man a man and stuff like that just out of nowhere
Just like a mental patient like screaming at you me and then she like he pushes her to a point where she's like
You know threatening to unalive somebody like and then I have to end the show because you know now it's gone way too far
It's like now it's like I can't have him pushing people like these edges
And it's like that's why I had oceans on the other night and God he was like
You know, trolling her, I got upset, you know, and I say, I love you, Gotti, and stuff like that, but I got upset because it's like, there's so many people that are just a good people and they get trolled for like no reason, and they're expecting it to never come by.
Gotti isn't a hateful troll.
You can't tell me
No, he said to ocean he said that she was a big fat broad or something like that
Wait a minute time out, but it's okay for you to let people call us skank skunks
You know old heads. I'm trying to look again. I can now like I mean it's like I've been trying to like stop it every time now
I've been trying to stop it. I know I'm talking to you, but I
Can't because I'm trying to explain
I'm trying to like come to the defense now. I'm coming you're coming to the defense to the wrong people
But I will come to your defense, but you know it hasn't happened in a long time that you were
Have you not noticed I've not been on panel
Okay, I've been under a lot of stress too lately and
Yeah, I mean no Christine has Christine has even when she hasn't been here she has you know, it's like
She's here she's here somewhere and Christine, you know, please it's like why don't come on panel though and the reason
I don't my best friend
I know every single thing Christine does you don't have to tell me shit and I know why she doesn't do because you know I
go online to have some fun blow off some steam joke and I control people like you know I control
just as you know not as good as others but you can do it without being hateful and I don't think I
might that's what I'm saying that's what I yeah that's what I'm saying I told you he was he was
You just don't like him because for whatever reason he gets underneath your
I do like him. I do like him. He was on the show all night earlier and then we had a great conversation
We got along we were fine. Absolutely. I know I like him a lot and we discussed it like about how I was like to him like
You know, I told him how I felt about what he said to her and stuff like that and like why I kicked him off that night
And he was just mad because I like, you know, he thought I was like, you know, still talking
Well, but if you start kicking off because somebody um makes fun of somebody
Then you better not have nobody on your panel. Yeah
Well, that's what I'm saying, but it didn't but that's what the but you know, the other
Hold on. Okay, but terrible calling somebody fat. That's one thing. This is the F
Actually, they have no clue if they're fat or not
But I you know, I came up on your panel the other day because you had somebody
Repeatedly using the F word it took you for him to say it three times
Are you finally to put them in back but Goddy call somebody fat?
Yeah, but I don't see the thing is I wasn't even against like that that word is like I don't have a problem with that word and
But when I was not modern, but it's like I'm actually when people describe as that word, you know
It's like you've been used against me. So I like I can take it back, you know
It's like well, maybe I identify as fat and I'm saying oh you're talking about that
But what I'm saying calling somebody fat or ugly or
How they go up to summer for tea or they go after me because I'm old, you know, I'm okay with those things
but when you start using flers and homophobic things and and
Things like that. That's where it stops
Yeah, but even that Christine and I get what you're saying. I do understand what you're saying
But you also I'm gonna go back to the foundation. He's late of this channel. Oh, yeah
That's the foundation he laid. So just sit there for a microman. Either either either either change what you're doing or
Don't micromanage everything because it all in this kind of a community. I don't give a fuck if you like the F word or not
That's the community
There wasn't that's what I'm saying
That's group to Christine's point. It's like it's like yeah, it's like I can't stop people using these words
I accept to tell them a million times and create songs and put rules up
Let's see my point
And to kind of bounce on Christine's point is okay. I get that she don't like the slurs
I don't like the flowers either but again
I understand the community that I am and I just thought what words fucking affect me
But the point is, my point that I'm going to make is that you can't sit there and you
know what I mean?
Don't know fuck it. It don't even matter. It's just it's it's the micromanaging
Christine and this kind of community is never gonna work and they're gonna do nothing about God you
This is what this is what I can create it. Okay. I want to say something
I am not trying to micromanic
But what I'm trying to say is that he got rid of somebody for calling somebody fat
But he leaves somebody up for using the F the other at Ford
That's the point 100% not say. Oh, well, you don't you can't have that because if there's people like me that don't want to hear
Hey, I won't be on panel B. I'll be a go to another channel. It's not a big deal
But you can't use oh well you said fat so you have to go. Oh you said f a and now you can stay
You see what I'm saying. I'm not micromanaging. You got to do
You're micromanaging. I'm saying that's what he's not doing. He he can't he can't do that
Because this is the fucking thing that he created.
He does micromanage with the wrong shit.
He lets people that are crazy as fuck say,
but people like Gotti that's fucking, you know,
I mean, don't get me wrong,
the guy that's fucking dirty, 100% he can.
But at the same time, I mean,
he uses kid's glove around here.
Yeah.
So for him to get banned for,
you know, how come my kid's glove,
as far as he's not going as hard as he could?
Add a respect cuz he likes you and you don't even see that
Well, I don't think I mean I say I don't consider even like a troll of me like you know
It's like I mean the thing was it's like
I had this lady on because he kind of likes you. You don't see that though. Uh-huh. I do see that
I do say I have a whole gaudy song, you know, I played it. He liked he loves it better like um
the uh
Yeah, so when oceans was on like first I first of all we had ray
And then we had jt and they both trolled her and I had to kick them off and then he came and then then
I'm also lld came up and trolled her too and it's like and then she's kind of like, you know
She's also a content creator. She's an older lady
Um, she's, um, you know, uh, really interesting and things like that.
Nobody else gets fucking passes on here.
No other woman sits here.
I watched you the other night.
Protect that lady when people, the rest of us, your female supporters, dude, I've had
people sit here and talk about my trafficking and all kinds of shit on your panel.
And that was fucking sad.
But this old lady comes in here and she gets trolled.
She ought to understand the community she is.
It bothers you more than bothered her.
No, she was pretty bothered, but it's like but I like I'm saying I will
You guys want me to defend you I think the only time I did the only time I didn't take somebody off it like so at your request if you
Summer would say take somebody off or whatever or even beta
It was the only time I ever really didn't do that was when she was telling me on panel this to take LC off or
LD or whatever his name is LD
and then to take him off and then but he hadn't done anything he was just telling
he was telling me to like kind of like assert power felt over me at that time
and because he hadn't done anything to like like on the panel to warrant that we were just
sitting around playing trivia or something and so that's the only time I like refused
like if any of you said take the person off I would you know and it's like never never
Did you guys I will say you do it for me, but I will say Christine has to play
No, I would you on it for me. No, but have you asked maybe if you ask that you
You said I demanded I told yeah, I told I told you I had a ban Alex for you
I will ban Alex I will like put it and writing and I will never ever have him on again
No, you can't say the words for me
You have but what you to I want you to go because you know I'm not I'm not you know
But you but you but Alex isn't your scapegoat for my channel because you're like I'm not gonna go to your channel
Alex is there and so if you're putting me in that channel and I just don't go there while he is there
No, no, no, you should bad Alex or what he has done to your channel just like flirting diamond. It's okay for her
Are him to porn bomb you you say you're never having them and here he is
Yeah, and we had some great shows and also flurry diamond did apologize to me in private like because
Well, yeah, but and I've said things about flurry diamond that I probably shouldn't have to and I've been kind of flipping and like
You know made some probably jokes that did hurt her feelings and like, you know, it's like it. That's my you know
I'm I'm not you know
I used to not have a thick skin and you can ask summer. I would cry at somebody my first time being called a cunt
Was on youtube. Oh my gosh. I was devastated. It was a nice summer. I was devastated
I
get up over the years from the founders. He was very fragile
That was a cycle path
And summer's lighting up so
You're welcome. You're welcome. You know what, thank you. This is what I'm going to say, sweetie.
I just think that, and I've noticed it, and I think it's great that you've found a population
on TikTok and other platforms, right? But I think you need to understand that you create
You can you could do anything you want, but it's gonna take you basically tearing your whole channel down and building your whole channel back up
Right, you've created this channel and it's going the way that you created it
Right good or bad and we have great times on this fuck a panel and we have shitty times on this panel
Right, it's it's what it is same thing with my panel. We have great times and sometimes we have shitty tops
Yeah
I think sometimes that since you've seen the other world of tick-tock and different things like that
You know, you're like, okay. Well, this is I want to you know
I want to change things over here and I want to do things over here, but your crowd hasn't changed
You know what I mean?
Now that will take time that will take time because and it's like because it's like but it's also like 80% of the people of
Subscribers of people here are returning subscribers like on the channel
and so there's very few people like new people coming in but at the same time the people that
are here are loyal and so it's like it's a it's a good thing and a bad it's a good thing it's good
and bad you know it's like and it's like I take the good with the bad here it's just like lately
I've been like kind of disappointed by people like you know I don't mind being trolled or like you
know people might like by like trolls making fun of me but it's like because I can you know why
you're stagnating your growth let me tell you why at least what I see a big part of it everybody
I'm putting your links in their channels when they go live
Because every time I go to channels and every time I go to channels like there's shit being talked about me
It's never done in the summers. I was at summers just the other day wasn't I summer
I was this is the other night and then I came on because now and I lurk a lot, right?
the guy with the guy um the guy random guy was in the chat sort of saying oh psych he's my bitch
you know because i donated he's my bitch just to get under your skin and you know i was there he
know i was there he didn't know i was there let me tell you something psychic whether you realize
this or not whether you realize this or not i every time i'm on the internet anywhere i'm at
Guess what? So does a lot of other trolls so because we all know how we all work including you so whether you're in chat or not
90% of time when you're not live and even when you are live because we hear the other phone playing sometimes
You're scanning other fucking chats
So they're gonna do that because they know that you're watching and they're gonna troll you
He wanted to come up and play his music because he thought he's he's a music whatever, you know, whatever y'all hide y'all little thing
It's gonna happen. You're on YouTube. You're on the internet if you think you're not gonna get trolled
Especially when you birth your shit out of the troll community, baby. Come on, you know better psyche
I know that is like that
Again, look at look at the amount of likes
Look at that. I have right now
Like um, it's gonna be like probably three or four or something like that
You're so worried about all that shit. You're not you don't care about your people anymore. I'm saying I'm saying I get
I get 10,000 likes on tick-tock in like 10 minutes
Here I can be out for 10 hours
You allow people troll in tick-tock. There's nobody on my panel. There's nobody comes on the panel or anything
It's just a random guy was in chat, and he was talking shit, and you got in your feet peas
No, I said, I said, I said, I'm not your bitch. That's all I said. And I get my fee fees. I just depended myself.
Yeah, you are in your fee fees because five days later and you're still talking about it.
Tick tock is no guys. I think I was at your show. I was just saying I was at your show the other day
That's what happened like but then I came on then I came on and like you know talk that I thought I was a good appearance
Everything I mean, I say I don't think it was
But I'm saying why don't get this shit, right? If I know like there's certain people I'm gonna fuck it home
Because then be and beat is like
I do go and beat his panel and then she'll like or then I'll get attacked by her by the people on the panel like by everybody and
It's like it's not fun
I was sleep because it's like they're just gonna tacked and like untrue stuff said as I can't even get a chance to defend
So why should you be any different than anybody else? You think everybody don't get attacked when they go on panel
Yeah, well, that's why we I thought I hang out in this community. So I can talk shit
Yeah, I'm not like I don't you know, I talk like you know talking shit like really I mean for me
It's like, you know, it's like not about people
You know, I like I like talking about like different things and like you know the world like the shit of the world
Right, but it's like I don't like talking shit about people that kind of thing
I know you don't either
What's that one chick the one live in Florida? Oh, Lisa. At least it
How many days did we you left us on panel and everything to go because you was so star-strung by this bitch
What do you think she goes through?
Yeah, yeah, I talked to her a lot
And what did she tell you ignore the silly shit
You think she'd be worse you that and with the number amount of viewers and people you think all those people like her
hate watchers
They love watching her spaz the fuck out. That's why she's so fucking famous.
Yep.
You know, my channel could blow up real fucking quick if I'd just spaz 24 fucking 7 because people love that shit.
Especially in the communities you've birthed your shit out of. Included by...
And you know, you always compare yourself to Howard Sturr, right?
You always compare yourself to Howard Sturr.
I can compare myself, but I mean, that was the kind of, the kind of show, it was the kind
of show.
I don't know.
I'm not, I'm not as a person, like, I don't know.
We're different people.
I mean, we are, I think a similar sense of humor somewhere.
I don't think you're similar at all.
Okay, well you don't have to I would say okay, well whatever I mean
I think I'm not saying that to be mean what I'm trying to tell you and
Yeah, if you want a Howard Stern type show
But you have it. I mean I had it. I had it. Yeah, but you want putty tap back
No, I mean it's like no, it's like the show. I just want the show like I like the show to be fun
Like you know, it's like it's like it's soft
it's just like with the
I know it's not it's not really fun right now. It's just like the constant criticism of every single thing
I do by like almost everybody including like friends and it's like, you know
It's like I'm not asking you to like to be like oh coddle the door and like you know
It lights you and everything but it's like I feel like I know I get no because I don't because I because I because I
Haven't at all. I would you know, maybe I would like that because I haven't received you know
All I get is hate and and it's like, you know, and that's what irritates me
This is what irritates me is because that is not all you get you have tons of people that fucking support you
And if support you through your crash outs through your drunken fucking nights through you not knowing your own fucking name
yep
Haven't left your fucking side
But you don't see that and that's what irritates me. So on that note. I love you guys. I will be in chat. I'm out
okay
It's not it's not it's not it's not the real Kate in the backstage. I know it's a fake Kate
And so just go away, please. It's not careless Kate
Careless Kate would like announce herself in chat and then I should have her as mod because I know it's the real her
but
Yeah, so you're not getting on fake careless Kate nice try Tony or
Alex or whatever like, you know, thanks guys for porn bombing me so much and like, you know
Even like, you know, I found out so can I point something out to like in the chat right now?
Okay, and don't do anything about it because it doesn't bother me. Hold on. Let me find the comment
Well, these old ladies are insane. Hold on a second. Where's the other one?
Hold on
I know somebody was calling us older, anyway, but you know, and all actually, they don't bother me, you scroll over shit like that.
When they call me an old hag, I scroll over shit like that.
You know what I can do Christine? I can I'll do so I can still do something about it. So hold on
Oh, it's a fake careless K. I know it's not the real careless
Well, then don't then put a screen up then put a screen up, but they're gonna say the n-word and I
It's not gonna hurt your channel. You know that, right? I still delete it
I just don't like it and it's like ugly and then he'll like it's
But yeah, but you know you can you can always keep your finger on the button and soon did you hear the sound boom?
I mean Christine like I give you like authority to like
You know you can't have the hiding authority and if like people like to see this person now
They're saying like yeah, you can like yeah something like you can just hide them if you want
No, there's no sense in hiding tiny, you know, I don't believe in hiding now
There's a few like tonight. I have had a couple because and earlier last night when it was the same people coming in with
You know 50 names at a time. Yeah, they were hidden because those are two trolls one does
Specifically hurt you or your channel. So they were specifically hidden. I don't try to hide people. I will time them out
But you know and and I'll be honest with you there were two people that normally do support your channel
I don't know what their problem was tonight you hid them
And I just went back and timed them out for 24 hours because I know you were you were feeling kind of blah
Tonight about what was going on and nobody was coming on panel and I and it's harder
it's easier to give them a timeout and let them come back after thinking about it than it is to
go through your blog or your hidden list and undo everybody. Yeah, but I'm glad. I mean,
some people like I ban I should like, you know, KZ was like, you know, like, remember, he like
was said, he's like said some weird comment about pores or whatever. And I was like, and then he's
like, Oh, he said, Oh, I meant my poor people. And I was like, Well, what'd you mean by like,
He's like, oh because you don't care about poor people or you don't like poor people or you have something against poor or something like that
And he just like just like attacks me again. And so
I'm glad I was hiding him. And yeah, so again guys go ahead and like if I ban somebody just leave them banned
And yeah, I think it goes like that. Oh, I don't want that person in the chat
It's not it's not the real Kate first of all, so I'm not being mean to Kate and stuff like that second of all, okay
Let me see. I'm just going to go through this and chat. I don't like them. I don't like them either,
Jamie. And so, yeah, I mean, it's like, I'm fine now. It's like, but I get in bad mood sometimes.
And it's like, and when I'm in a bad mood, and it's like, and then I, but I like feel like I want
to like, you know, like keep the stream consistent and stream every day. And sometimes I don't feel
like up to it. And it's like, I still do it. And it's like, and it's hard when
Constantly and it's if I don't know if you've seen like tonight, but it's like we just had such a problem with like this one troll
Like they kept coming on different accounts different accounts different account. Yeah, I was here
I was the one hiding them earlier or last night. Yeah, I mean I did it was the same
It had to have been same person and I probably hid 25 of their accounts. Yeah, so thank you Christine
I mean, I know you got my back and everything and it's like
But yeah, it was just like
When I think after another after another after it's just like it probably was just a few people and stuff like that
But sometimes it wears on me when I'm not in a good mood. I'll be back
And that's what I felt it was tonight. That is why the two they really
Oh, I bet it was Alex to some no no way of sans or butts
But I just felt these two normally
Don't act this way two of them that you hid and that's why I just went back in and I timed them out for 24 hours
Yeah, and the guys so I just want to say so I'm looking at my things right now
It says five likes five dislikes
Okay, and then 24% engagement that means like one out of four people in the chat are commenting
Okay, that means that five people have disliked it or five accounts have disliked it and five people have liked it
Okay, those five we hid there were trolls that you know, it doesn't matter. It's still you're getting they don't use those dislikes against you
High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High like to dislike rate. High
They don't they don't they don't show them, but they do count
I think to YouTube and the algorithm and stuff like that and some of these engage some of the engagements are really low like it's like
You know, there's like 20% engagement. I mean one in five people are
You also have to remember you have done some very
Short ones lately and I'll be honest your normal times that you're on when I wake up in the middle night
My early mornings was what your middle the night is
You used to be around you're not around now. I can go over to tiktok can see you
Yeah, but just for an hour a day and today I did like 20 minutes like tiktok's hard because they always say
Now it's like now it's like nine likes nine dislikes so former people since I said that like that
Well because you're bringing attention to it hon and they know it's bothering you
Yeah, just don't bring attention to it
Okay
Oh, yeah, okay. I'm just gonna end the stream. Well, thank you, Christine, for being here.
Wait a minute. See, this is what I want to talk about. Why are you ending the stream?
Because you saw all your graphics and you don't like the way they look and you feel blah about it.
Put up your big boy pants and keep it moving.
Yeah, but now yeah, but now it's like, you know, now it's like they'll just go even harder on it
No, they're not this is we're coming at 7 a.m. East Coast time people are starting to wake up
Okay, I just like I'm a little
Don't let it get to you that much, you know, I'm telling you I had a thin skin my god my world came crashing the first time
I was called a cunt
I
Can laugh at it now. I didn't laugh so much before and now I pride myself in being the cunt, okay?
Okay
I know their words and that's why it's like sometimes I'm like I'm not that I don't go that crazy about it
And it's like and then people get mad at me because I I didn't and I know some people have gone way too far and sometimes
I think it's like for comedic value and stuff and it's like you know
Just part of the drama of the show and it's hard to like then it's like when people's feelings really get hurt
And it's like and now I can't do anything about it
It's like but I've learned feeling to get hurt. You don't belong on social media
Yeah, unless unless you're in the under 18 or the G ratings
Yeah, you're gonna get hurt
But I think I'm just like I'm seeing some of the comments in the chat right now
And I'm just like and then I just feel like it's gonna it's going all bad right now. I'm gonna
Christie, yeah
They just came in and said hey everyone
Amanda saying how she doesn't I know they're back they're back stage
I mean the stage when they want to come on too, but it's awesome. Well, who's backstage?
I was good morning. Hi
Hey, Isaiah. Good morning sunshine. How you doing? Good. How are you? I'm good
Here who's the other one?
So one little thing
All right, so in any business doing market research is very, very important.
You need to know who your main audience is going to be.
Then there's segments of the market that you need to focus on.
One thing that you allow to happen is that for the sake of views,
You allow a community that is very based around